THE LOVE LAB
Now, the third king's privilege
will be announced.
Right away?
You cannot check
your own Heart Boxes today.
Only the king
can open everyone's Heart Box.
Only the king can see
the result of everyone's Heart Chip vote.
-Even the notes?
-I want to do it.
I want to be king.
I think he voted for me,
and of course, Ga-yeon
since he voted for both of us
yesterday as well.
I did think that Jung-min
and Kyung-ho probably voted for me,
so I wasn't curious
about the number of hearts.
I just wanted to see the notes.
The first thing I wondered was
if they'll be delivered at some point.
And I also wondered
what I'd do if it didn't get delivered.
The message was something
that I really wanted to say.
I wondered if Ga-yeon voted for me or not,
how much she put in,
and what she wrote on the note.
I'm most curious about those.
If you are curious about your Heart Box,
you must win the favor of the king
to get the information.
Second,
the king will find out
everyone's Heart Chip colors.
Really?
-Nice.
-Must be nice.
Wow. Nice.
The king gets to know everything, then.
I was a bit taken aback when I heard that.
What am I supposed to do
after I look at all of that by myself?
My head hurt a lot.
I thought I'd get the power
to choose the dates.
To be honest, that's why
Ye-rim made me king.
But because I didn't have
that important power,
I was startled.
Third, the king may choose
a man and woman
to spend the night in the tent.
No way.
-No way.
Kyung-ho and Ye-rim?
Seriously, no.
-Kyung-ho and Ye-rim…
-You go out.
Let me say this nicely,
you and Chae-rin should go out, okay?
I mean it.
…choose a man and woman
to spend the night in the tent.
Today's king, Park Do-geon,
shall go to the Heart Room
to check everyone's Heart Chip
and Heart Box.
Sounds fun.
Should we carry you there?
-Sounds fun.
-See you.
Okay.
Remember well this time.
He forgets everything.
Even the colors of his own hearts.
He forgets mine too.
I really did forget.
What's the color of your hearts?
Isn't it pink?
ACTING LIKE SHE DOESN'T KNOW
I don't know. I don't remember
the colors I got on the first day.
Can you remember them?
I should take a piece of paper.
Take some paper.
-Take a piece of paper?
-He seriously should.
EVERYONE'S HEART CHIP JAR
HAS THEIR NAME ON IT
EACH BOX SHOWS THE CURRENT
HEART CHIP STATUS AND NAMES OF THE VOTERS
HA-YOON: 66
YE-RIM: 205, CHAE-RIN: 1, HYE-WON: 26
JUNG-MIN: 63
DO-GEON: 24
HYE-WON, HA-YOON, YE-RIM, JUNG-MIN,
DO-GEON, GA-YEON, CHAE-RIN, KYUNG-HO
CHECKING THE RESULT
OF HIS OWN HEART CHIPS FIRST
PARK DO-GEON
YE-RIM: 205, CHAE-RIN: 1, HYE-WON: 26
PARK DO-GEON, GONGGI
GOOD LUCK!
TIME TO GO ON A DATE WITH ME
I felt sure about Chae-rin
after seeing that.
I was most curious about
where Kyung-ho's feelings
were leaning toward.
I'M ROOTING FOR THE QUEEN
GA-YEON'S BOX
KYUNG-HO: 40, JUNG-MIN: 16
Since Kyung-ho voted for Ga-yeon,
I figured he has feelings for her.
But when I read his note,
he told her to choose what she wants.
I recall it being a long note
with that kind of message on it.
After seeing that,
I thought, "What does that mean?"
Then, are these Heart Chips
his final message to her?
I thought it was very vague.
KING DO-GEON WRITES THEM DOWN
SO HE WON'T FORGET
MEANWHILE, IN THE LIVING ROOM
Who voted for Do-geon?
No one fell for that.
-The women did.
-I didn't…
Someone made a deal with Do-geon
and promised to give him
a bunch of hearts.
Like 100 hearts. All for Do-geon.
-It could have been 200.
-Yeah, 200.
"Let's get along."
"You're the puppet king.
I'm the real king."
It could have been something like that.
That's jumping to conclusions though.
I was in a really foul mood
after he said that.
I did go on a date with Do-geon
and I didn't think that
Kyung-ho wouldn't know
about my alliance or plot with Do-geon.
Did he have to say that
in front of everyone?
Is he saying that
because he didn't like what I did?
He said "puppet king" sarcastically.
Can the king not choose the dates then?
Today's camping is going to be important.
He's going to see all the notes I wrote.
That's annoying.
What did you write?
-How cheesy was it?
-Did you propose to her?
I think Do-geon's expression
is going to be hilarious.
DO-GPT OVERLOAD
JUST THEN, A HEART BOX
CAUGHT DO-GEON'S EYE
LEE YE-RIM
0 HEARTS
MOMENTS AGO
KYUNG-HO PUT HEART CHIPS
INTO GA-YEON'S BOX
KYUNG-HO DID NOT PUT
ANY HEART CHIPS INTO YE-RIM'S BOX
Honestly, I had no idea
what I could do for her.
Was telling her everything
the right thing to do or staying quiet?
I was feeling overwhelmed.
If I told her the truth,
it may hurt her rather than help her.
So I was very cautious.
-The king has returned.
-Oh, no.
Gosh. I'm done being king.
Come here.
Please leave.
-He wrote them down.
-He has a lot of paper.
I see.
-What?
-I see.
What's up with him?
Oh, I see.
-What is it that you see?
-What is it?
Are those the notes you wrote down?
-The ones you recorded?
-Take them.
-Let's knock him out.
-Take them from him.
If you're curious about anything,
win my favor.
I can tell you if you want.
-Really,
-Yes.
sir?
"Sir?"
I have to decide who sleeps outside.
That's right.
I really want to
sleep inside.
Your face is radiant today.
It has been radiant this whole time.
Should the person who thinks they'll go
try to win him over?
If you have a bad feeling about it?
-I have a bad feeling about me.
-I do.
I really do.
Close your eyes and I'll pick two people.
-Those two can go.
-Okay.
Are you thinking straight, Do-geon?
I'm counting on you.
I can't wait to see
how Do-geon handles this.
-Don't pick Ye-rim!
-I think he'll pick Ye-rim.
I'm scared.
Oh. Please don't?
We have to be like,
"Please don't pick us."
I'm scared.
I'm really scared.
Do-geon, please.
HE CHOOSES YE-RIM TO SLEEP IN THE TENT
HE CHOOSES KYUNG-HO TO SLEEP IN THE TENT
Okay, I'm done choosing.
You see? You see?
How is she supposed to sleep?
-It was as I expected.
-You know what? This is for the better.
They can make up overnight.
Ye-rim did want to
have a conversation with him.
-Instead of being frustrated…
-Yeah.
-…it's better to talk one-on-one.
Okay, I'm done choosing.
-Really?
-You chose?
-I'm really scared.
-Who was chosen?
-I think it's these two.
-I think so too.
-I know.
-That's my guess.
-He didn't choose me though.
-Really?
He's acting.
-He really didn't choose me.
-What?
-Who was chosen?
It's you, isn't it?
It's me.
-Ye-rim and Kyung-ho?
-Is that right?
That feels weird.
Have fun.
Do we go now?
-What?
-No, later.
We can go later when we sleep.
He must really not want to go.
He said it wasn't him.
He said he had a bad feeling
before it even started
and he knew he would get chosen.
Did he have to be so obvious
that he didn't want to go?
The thing is,
everyone noticed that Kyung-ho and I
were initially interested in each other.
And everyone knew that
the vibe changed after the first date.
So did he have to go that far?
I was very upset about that.
THE 3RD KING STARTED RULING
-Let me get straight to the point.
-Okay.
Kyung-ho voted for Ga-yeon.
He gave her about 63 hearts.
Sixty…
KYUNG-HO GAVE GA-YEON 40 HEARTS
63 hearts?
Kyung-ho gave her 40 hearts.
He gave her 40 hearts.
And on the note,
well…
What did it say? Hang on.
Anyway, Ye-rim invested
her Heart Chips in me,
I wanted to repay her kindness.
I had to repay Ye-rim's kindness.
Hold on.
-Do-geon!
-He's so clumsy.
He wrote something in the vein of
hoping she'd make her own choice.
"I'll make the choice for you."
THE HEART CHIP INFO GOES OFF TRACK
If someone smart like Ha-yoon did it,
he would have done a good job.
And when I looked carefully
at Kyung-ho's note…
So the reason why Kyung-ho
voted for Ga-yeon was because
he wanted to give her the note.
He gave her 40 hearts to do that?
I know, right?
Maybe he wanted to make her king.
But Ga-yeon wanted to
make Jung-min king.
She gave him 163 hearts.
And she wrote,
"Let's have some fun tomorrow."
How many did he give her?
Maybe he didn't.
He didn't.
-He didn't?
-No.
-Isn't it the first time he hasn't voted?
-Yeah.
-He's trying to make it clear.
-Right.
He must have thought we were
going to check our boxes today.
If he didn't give you any despite that…
Exactly. He wants me to know that
he didn't choose me.
Gosh, this is giving me a headache.
"I'll make a choice for you?"
No, it was,
"Make the choice for yourself."
Then, Kyung-ho is totally into Ga-yeon.
-But Ga-yeon gave Jung-min 163 hearts?
-Yeah.
Right. I think
-Kyung-ho chose Ga-yeon.
-Yeah.
But Ga-yeon wants Jung-min.
"I choose you. But you decide
for yourself." Isn't that it?
-It could be that.
-I think you're right.
He really wanted to make it clear.
Even the day before,
he gave me Heart Chips
and said he had a good time
despite being very vague with me.
The fact that he didn't give me any…
He didn't even know
we weren't going to check our Heart Chips.
so he really left
no room for interpretation.
He didn't put any in my box
even though he thought I'd check it.
And I have to spend the night with him?
I should have decided the camping thing
after talking this over.
That's why I was like, "Huh?"
You acted too quickly.
I should've just gone
to the tent with you.
-Can you take it back?
-No.
You did well, Do-geon.
-If you…
-If the two of you left,
I might have joined you there.
Like sleeping with mom and dad.
They have just changed roles with me
from yesterday.
This time, the guy is sure,
but the girl is saying,
"I like you too
but I'm not sure yet, so please wait."
What do we do about you?
Tell me.
-About what?
-The notes.
-The notes?
-Yes.
Tell me.
Why should I?
What can I do for you?
I'm curious about what the notes say.
I already know who gave me the notes.
-It's two, isn't it?
-Who?
-Kyung-ho and…
-Why do you think that?
-Because Kyung-ho told me today.
-What did he say?
-Hmm?
-Why did he say he'd vote for you?
He didn't say he'd vote for me.
I think he expressed how he felt.
-How he felt?
-Yeah.
Hmm.
Jung-min's message
was about how he liked you.
He said something like,
"I'm rooting for you."
What about Kyung-ho?
Ask him.
He won't tell me.
I don't think he'll tell me.
Kyung-ho.
Congratulations on sleeping outside.
-Me?
-What did you write?
-What did I write?
-On the note.
-Why?
-Because I'm curious.
-It's kind of cheesy to say it out loud.
-What did you write?
I put a lot of effort into it.
That's why I'm curious.
I thought you would.
I can't say it. I can't say it out loud.
-I can do it in writing.
-Yeah? Then, write it for me.
-Okay, I'll do it later.
-Okay.
Okay.
What did Ga-yeon ask you just now,
Your Majesty?
-Come and have a seat here, your Majesty.
-She kept asking about her notes.
-Oh, in her box?
-Yeah.
Jung-min.
What?
What were you about to say?
-What was I about to say?
-Yeah.
I was just going to say,
"You got this, Jung-min."
-Really?
-Yeah.
Ga-yeon, the king told me that I got this.
Why?
"You got this?"
What did you write?
Me?
-I'll tell you later.
-Come on.
I really gave you a lot.
Really?
I wanted to make you king.
So why didn't you become king?
I think the rest were determined
to make Do-geon king.
-Really?
-They conspired together.
Why?
I think they plotted something
just like us that one time.
-I put most of mine in yours.
-Really?
And
I left a little and put most in yours.
-Really?
-Yeah.
What a shame. I wish I could have checked
that I had your full support.
I know. I thought for sure you'd be king.
You were the only one though.
Ga-yeon must have told him
that she's still thinking about it.
Despite that,
he only voted for her and told her
to vote the way she wants?
Were his feelings stronger than expected?
He may be into himself for doing that.
Do you want to have a chat with him?
I don't even know
if there's any room for that.
If he had just told me
that's what he decided to do,
I would have accepted that.
But he just treats me like I'm invisible.
He really never looks at me.
And they act like they are
the only two people in the world.
-Can we pause it briefly?
-Yeah.
Ye-rim also
had a part in not trying hard enough.
like trying to start a conversation
with him or something.
Kyung-ho may be pleasantly surprised
at the confident side of Ye-rim.
She could have created opportunities
to change the atmosphere.
But she just stayed back by herself
and would just hear the opinions
of others around her.
How could things have improved
under these circumstances?
She keeps talking about
how he didn't make eye contact with her,
but because she has feelings for him,
all of her attention is towards him,
so it just feels that way.
-I've been in that exact position.
-Yeah?
If I keep looking at him
but he never looks at me?
Also, I'm not just anybody.
I was someone he was into once.
So I would be very disappointed
if he didn't look at me once.
Yeah, I get that.
It's frustrating
because she reminds me of myself.
I'm learning a life lesson from this.
Since Kyung-ho and I are
going to talk this evening,
I was fixing my makeup.
Even after Heart Chip votes
and even before the announcement,
he didn't look at me once.
-Who wants to see the Big Dipper outside?
-Me.
-You found it?
-Yeah.
I thought it was weird.
I thought we had plenty of time to talk.
-Come over here.
-Come here, Ga-yeon.
But he sat next to Ga-yeon,
and kept making eye contact with her
and joking around.
He did it so obviously.
-No, I don't want to.
-Let's have only Ga-yeon do it.
Ga-yeon is smart.
It really felt like he was
treating me like I was invisible.
Kyung-ho used to sit next to me.
Come over here.
It was mostly the two of us talking then.
But he suddenly disappeared
and went over there.
I felt all alone.
If he wants to act natural,
he can look at me at least, right?
That's what's so mean about him.
At first, I thought
if the two of them were happy together,
I was okay with it.
But his actions are so mean that
I don't want them to be together.
Tell me this one thing.
Did it turn out the way you expected
or was there anything that was surprising?
-I kind of had an idea about most people…
-Yeah?
…but I couldn't figure you out.
-Really?
-Yeah.
But you can see it now, right?
I made it pretty clear.
-Have you made up your mind now?
-I think so.
You think so?
-I have.
-You have?
Hmm…
Actually, Ga-yeon became my choice.
That's how I feel.
But this is what I'm cautious about.
The date itself was so fun for me.
I said what I wanted to say
and heard what I wanted to hear.
And it helped me feel more at ease.
But I'm wondering if I am
totally drawn towards Ga-yeon
because I was briefly swayed by that
or that feeling was still lingering.
That's why I want to think about it
one last time
until tomorrow morning just to be safe.
Got it.
Whose are you most curious about?
Ga-yeon and Ye-rim's.
First of all, Ye-rim voted for you.
She voted for you,
but she didn't give you a lot.
Why didn't she give you a lot?
She thought the king could
decide tomorrow's dates,
so she gave me over 200 hearts
-to make me king.
-Okay.
I thought Kyung-ho ought to know that.
This is how strong
Ye-rim's feelings are towards him.
-I was surprised too.
-Right?
I was like "She invested in me this much?"
That's how much she likes you.
It seemed like she has
very strong feelings for you.
But she thinks she didn't get
a chance to talk with you a lot.
That is true.
We were both awkward
since it was the first date.
She was really bummed about it.
-Well, she doesn't know how you feel.
-Right.
Thank you for telling me honestly.
I definitely thought I needed to talk
with Ye-rim, more so than Ga-yeon.
I'll do my best to
end it well or something.
I have to be honest no matter what.
But that's what's so hard right now.
I was feeling very conflicted.
I wanted to chat more with Ga-yeon too,
so I wanted to stay inside but…
Smell this. Doesn't it smell good?
Don't you want some?
You have to leave soon.
Not soon. I'll leave when it's bedtime.
I have to wash up.
It's not like I wasn't going to
have a conversation with Ye-rim.
But it wasn't going to be
anything nice for her to hear.
I worried about how we were going to sleep
after saying that.
I was going through all kinds of emotions.
That's why I was being hesitant when…
What time is it now?
-Two o'clock.
What time will you go out?
I'm not sure.
Come on. Isn't that hurtful?
It's driving me nuts.
He looks like he's dragging his feet
because he doesn't want to go.
-Yeah.
-"Do you hate me that much?"
"Didn't you say you liked me before?"
How can he change his mind in a day?
If the king decided, do as he says!
This makes me angry.
Wash up right now!
What time will you go out?
I'm not sure.
How about 2:30 a.m.?
Go out at 2:30 a.m.?
-I can go out now.
-Really?
-Let's go out at 2:30 a.m.
-Okay.
This is making me sick.
Let's just talk or maybe go back inside.
THE AGREED-UPON 2:30 A.M. CAME
Why did it have to be sleeping outside?
What do you think about sleeping outside?
It doesn't matter to me
whether we sleep outside or not.
Okay.
I don't care if I have to.
What are you eating?
It was nothing.
What?
Is there something you want to talk about?
Can you go…
-Go first?
-Yeah.
It would be better for you
if I went straight to the point, right?
-No.
-No?
No.
How did your date go today?
It was fun.
What did you do? Foot bath?
-Yeah, foot bath and barbecue.
-Foot bath and barbecue?
You can't go wrong with barbecue.
You should've asked for chicken.
HEH
She's being prepped to be dumped.
She's facing the chopping block.
In historical dramas,
they're on their knees,
waiting to be executed.
But the executioner keeps spraying water
on his sword
but doesn't kill him.
It's so frustrating.
He keeps spraying water on his sword
and swings it but doesn't kill them.
They wait for their head
to get chopped off.
She can start the conversation though.
-This is the thing. Ye-rim likes him.
-Yeah.
-There's no scenario where she dumps him.
-Right.
She's waiting because
Kyung-ho has to make the choice.
It's so frustrating.
Kyung-ho frustrates me.
Ye-rim frustrates me.
Ye-rim frustrates me too.
Let's watch. I got worked up.
Is that what you wanted to tell me?
-What I wanted to tell you?
-Yeah.
-No.
-I know.
You didn't want me to get to the point.
I meant that you didn't have to
make it so brief.
I told you this yesterday.
I said I needed to
be sure about my feelings.
The thing is, I'm still unsure.
It has only been two days since we met.
I get that we don't have much time
and it's too short to
get to know someone else.
Honestly, there's someone
I am still curious about
and I don't want to feel like
I have to force myself to let go.
So I wanted to go on a date
with Ga-yeon today
and I wanted to
sort out how I felt.
I eventually went on the date
and I was able to
sort it out a bit on my own.
For today's choice, I went with Ga-yeon.
The reason for that is
because I like
Ga-yeon…
more.
That's how I feel right now.
I don't want to be hasty by saying that
I only have eyes for her right now.
But I am going to
make up my mind by early morning
and that is all I can really say to you.
It's not that I didn't expect to hear
what you just told me.
It doesn't matter to me at all
that you chose Ga-yeon.
What I don't understand is
the way you acted.
How did I act?
You could have just told me.
About what? How I felt?
You could have just told me
what was going on.
I was really going to tell you today.
-When?
-Within the day.
There wasn't any time to talk
in the first place.
There was a lot of time.
You just avoided me.
I guess it appeared like I avoided you.
-Yeah, I did avoid you.
-Yeah.
I could tell you were avoiding me.
I didn't know why you had to be that way.
I thought it was a bit rude.
I really wasn't avoiding you.
-Really?
-I was being cautious.
It is very hard for me to
talk about this with you.
It's harder because it's you.
I didn't think it was a situation where
I could call you as soon as I saw you
and say, "Let's hash it out."
At least, it wasn't like that for me.
I guess I did avoid your gaze
since I couldn't look at you.
I just feel sorry.
If you felt sorry, I don't think
you should've acted that way with Ga-yeon.
I don't know how Ga-yeon and I acted but…
I'm getting PTSD.
What is this?
-Kyung-ho is actually…
-It's like the show EXchange.
…speaking honestly right now.
How are they supposed to sleep now?
It would be so uncomfortable.
Don't sleep there.
Just go to your respective beds.
Tell the king that you can't do it.
It's up to the king.
The two of you kept exchanging
non-verbal signals to one another.
Talking about a puppet king and whatnot.
And you said you had a bad feeling
about sleeping outside
and that you didn't want to do it.
I was just going along with everyone.
It would be weird for me to say
that I didn't care about sleeping outside.
That's why…
I guess you can
put meaning to everything I say and do,
but it wasn't like that for me.
Oh.
I don't know.
To be honest, I got a bit irritated.
She kept dismissing everything I said.
It seems like no matter what I say,
you can't accept it.
I wonder if the way
I expressed myself was wrong.
I wonder if it was completely wrong.
I really don't know.
Think about it, Kyung-ho.
Okay.
If you didn't have any feelings for me,
would you have said those things?
-To you?
-Yeah.
If it were me,
I wouldn't have done those things
if I didn't have feelings for you.
What about you?
Would you ask me out?
You and Ga-yeon like each other,
but isn't Ga-yeon also curious
about Jung-min too?
The way you feel
is the way I felt yesterday.
Let's say Ga-yeon went on a date
with Jung-min under those circumstances.
She starts avoiding you,
keeps sitting next to Jung-min,
and exchanges looks with him.
I wonder how you would react
in that situation.
If I were in that situation,
the first thing that I would do
is to try to do something about it.
So what would you have done?
I'd wonder what I did wrong
and what I was lacking.
-That would be the first thing
-Exactly.
-I would do.
-Yeah.
Can you just hear me out?
I get the feeling that
Ye-rim is trying to control Kyung-ho.
Why does she have to know
why he doesn't like her?
That's how he feels.
He's entitled to do what he wants.
Objectively speaking,
Ye-rim is in the wrong.
Do you know what the issue is?
The reason why she's upset?
She wasn't the one who initiated it.
He flirted with her.
Then, with no transition in the middle,
he just ignored her.
It was either flirting or ignoring.
There was no friendship or mutual respect
as a human being.
That's how she feels.
Anyway,
one person isn't interested
and the other person is interested.
That's why she can't be objective.
He can see this situation objectively
since he isn't interested in her.
But Ye-rim was never able
to think objectively
because her feelings were that big.
This is the issue.
I've always felt this when I had a crush.
You can't hate someone
just because you once liked them.
It can't be used as a weapon.
But if you like someone so much,
it becomes a weapon.
You think you can hate someone
as much as you liked them.
-Right.
-You feel justified doing it.
That's really bad though.
Yeah,
that's what drives the other person crazy.
Exactly. But you can only fix it
when you go through it yourself.
I think Ye-rim will also regret it
when she sees this.
-My heart was aching because…
-Ye-rim.
…she's doing exactly what I did.
I feel so uncomfortable.
This is going to be a hit.
I think I would've tried harder.
How would I know?
But…
if it were me,
I wouldn't have given up.
But
I wouldn't want to burden them either.
That's it.
I see.
In my case,
regardless of giving up or not,
I think I would have been
disappointed by their actions.
Of course, I can't be a good person to you
since I didn't act the way you wanted.
I don't know how many things
you don't understand.
No, I do understand.
I understand it from your perspective.
Then, what do you want to tell me?
You understand me but you're disappointed.
Is that it?
I understand you,
but what you did was bad.
I had no choice but to act badly.
But no matter how nice I was to you,
-I would've seemed bad to you.
-Sure.
What is it now?
I really hate it when someone
speaks to me in a sarcastic tone.
So I wondered if she was talking to me
like that to provoke me
or it felt that way to me
because I was too sensitive.
Why? What is it?
How do you want me to say it?
Hmm?
But did I really
act so irresponsibly?
As I told you yesterday,
I didn't want to give an uncertain answer
and that's why I needed time.
And I should be the one
to decide that time
since I was the one that needed time.
I didn't forget about it
and I was definitely going to tell you.
I just needed some time to prepare.
Why are you so hesitant
to bring that up to me?
Of course, I should be.
-Shouldn't I?
-But I don't know what you're thinking.
You were really my first choice.
I guess I believed that
our relationship was difficult
to walk away from.
That's why I did that.
Okay.
You have nothing more to say, right?
-Me?
-Yeah.
I am really
sorry that I acted that way.
I have nothing else.
Me neither.
I want to go on a date tomorrow.
We haven't been able to
have a conversation yet.
-Didn't we talk a lot?
-Well…
-A heartfelt one?
-Yeah.
We haven't had that.
-We held hands in front of the fireplace.
-Not that.
We talked while starting the fire.
"Fire."
Something more…
-More meaningful?
-Yeah.
-Shall we go to bed at 3 a.m.?
-Okay.
Let me see this.
It's not good to wear
a bandage for too long.
Come on. This is nothing, right?
I'm a man.
Let's be friends.
Why are you laughing?
Okay.
Thanks.
I think I'm going to cry.
"Let's be friends" must be
the most absurd thing ever for Kyung-ho.
Let's be friends?
After tormenting me emotionally?
That's probably what
Kyung-ho is thinking.
I'm gonna cry.
I'm serious.
Ye-rim must have had
so many thoughts from there.
-I'm sure.
-So many thoughts.
I'm sure it won't be easy to be friends.
I mean, she probably felt sorry
and felt like she reacted immaturely,
so she wanted to make things less awkward.
That's why she just said that.
She should've said sorry sooner.
I don't want to be friends with you.
Kyung-ho said sorry.
Why should Ye-rim feel so sorry?
Ye-rim viewed things emotionally
only in the way she wanted.
I understand how she feels,
but I understand how Kyung-ho feels too.
If Kyung-ho apologized,
Ye-rim should apologize too.
It was
a very clumsy expression of her feelings
when she said, "Let's be friends."
-Hold on.
-This is unbelievable.
-It's just that…
-Yeah?
…I got too immersed in this. Oh, no.
Seriously though,
-I was in a similar situation.
-Yeah?
But I was also…
I guess I'm not over it.
I made a situation worse like her once.
I interpreted things so badly.
I read into things too much.
When the mood got really tense,
I said something like that too.
I just said,
"Let's make up and be friends."
Just like her.
I tried…
You see, my friends would take my side
when I criticize the person I liked.
Even though they knew I was wrong,
they would all take my side.
So I ended up really hating that person,
but when Joo-heon explained
how he must have felt,
I thought of my own mistakes
and felt so bad all of a sudden.
I saw so much of myself in Ye-rim.
There's one more thing that I want to say.
Kyung-ho wasn't someone
who could handle a woman like Ye-rim.
Two people with the same capacity
-can't make room for each other.
-Unbelievable.
But someone with a bigger capacity
can always make room for the smaller.
When Ye-rim acts that way,
she needs to meet someone
who can embrace her.
The same applies for you too.
That person didn't have the capacity
to handle you.
I hope they don't get the wrong idea.
There were many guys that I liked.
-That's why--
-How many were there?
-I don't want anyone to get it wrong.
I don't want them to think
that I was crying because of them.
It isn't anyone recent.
It's not from this year.
It isn't the recent person
you said you met?
-Oh, not him?
-No, before him.
Gosh, this is new.
After I got back from the date,
it was nice when I was just with Jung-min,
without Kyung-ho around.
Of course.
But if you were with Jung-min?
You'd miss Kyung-ho.
Yeah.
Jung-min is the safe choice.
But the excitement
and the strong attraction
is Kyung-ho.
It isn't that I don't like Jung-min.
It's different. You see…
I'll head out first.
What do I do now?
Did you sleep well, Ye-rim?
It must've been so uncomfortable.
He slept so well next to me though.
After talking so much with him,
I didn't want to try to
make a move on Kyung-ho anymore.
You look good together.
-Do this pose.
-What?
If I had to choose,
Do-geon's my second choice.
But I didn't want to take
the time away from those two either.
Then, what am I supposed to do now?
-Is it a devil?
-Yeah.
-How was it in the tent?
-The tent?
There isn't much to say.
I fell asleep before I even knew it.
I was so tired.
Did you eat anything?
Yeah, I had a sandwich.
So this morning,
Jung-min was lying on the couch
while Kyung-ho was seated and drawing.
I felt my body leading me one way.
Of course.
-My head was going towards Jung-min.
-Of course, it's different.
I think you should go for Kyung-ho.
-You were leaning…
-I can't be like this.
There's nothing you can't be.
Dating someone like Jung-min
is the right choice.
But my eyes keep drifting toward Kyung-ho.
-I'm drawn to him.
-Yeah.
-My body just goes to him.
-Of course.
He's handsome.
Gosh.
My head hurts.
Why must I endure such hardship?
It's a good thing
since it means you're popular.
Did you sleep well?
-I have so much on my mind.
-Why?
My eyes keep drifting toward Kyung-ho.
It's like--
If I were you, I wouldn't change my mind.
This comes down to
a difference in people's personalities,
so it's hard to suggest
a direction for you.
In the beginning,
I only had romantic feelings for Jung-min.
But Kyung-ho is the one that
draws my attention.
You don't know why
but you're drawn to him?
I don't know why. I'm just drawn to him.
Our eyes met so many times,
so I asked him
if he usually looks at people like that.
Kyung-ho makes proper eye contact.
-Right?
-I think he's just like that.
I thought I made a lot of
eye contact with him too,
so I honestly had the wrong idea.
It's a bit embarrassing to say,
but I thought he was interested in me.
He looks at people like that.
-He gazes at you.
-With depth.
I feel captivated.
Look at Do-geon.
-I feel at ease.
-Look at Do-geon.
Me too.
HE WAS JUST EATING HIS CUP NOODLES
I had no interest in Jung-min.
In fact, I was more interested in Do-geon.
Do-geon and Kyung-ho.
But holding hands played a huge part.
I haven't experienced that.
Am I in denial right now?
Of course.
That's why you're more drawn to him.
You'd feel sorry for some people
if you chose Kyung-ho.
-Jung-min and Ye-rim.
-Maybe you can't make up your mind
because of that.
I have a lot on my mind right now.
The two men are so different.
It's so hard
and I don't know
how I feel exactly either.
We must've gotten something.
THE SECRET DATE BEGINS NOW
YOUR DATE AND YOUR DESTINATION IS A SECRET
EVERYONE MUST LEAVE NOW
"Tomorrow is the day
for secret conversations."
"You'll have the chance to secretly have
a one-on-one conversation with
the person you're interested in."
"Text the person's name you'd like to have
a secret conversation with tomorrow."
"You can request up to
two people of the opposite sex."
Up to two people?
Gosh.
I had more questions to ask him.
Why does he want to choose me?
I was hoping it wasn't simply because
I was the first person he spoke to.
Through the secret conversations,
I wanted to confirm my feelings
for Jung-min and Kyung-ho.
I needed to talk to Ga-yeon
since we may not get to go on a date.
Rather than having a secret conversation,
I think we'll just go out on a date.
Do you know where we have to go?
CAFE BONJOUR
SECRET DATE
Huh?
This place looks familiar.
Didn't the bad picture-taking two
take pictures here?
You're right!
Are you reusing previous locations?
Come on!
Yeah, the two that were
bad at taking photos.
You scared me!
CHAE-RIN AND DO-GEON
SECRET DATE
I was so startled.
When did you get here?
Maybe about five minutes ago?
Anything you want to ask me?
I want to know
who you're going to see today.
That's what you want to know?
Of course. You aren't curious about that?
I'm curious too.
Really?
I'm not going to tell you.
-Did you request two people?
-What?
What?
Who knows?
I may have requested two people.
You said you had a second choice.
You were curious about two.
I don't know who that is.
Do you want to know?
Of course I would.
-Are you curious?
-Yeah.
Actually, I knew who it was.
But I wanted to hear it directly from him.
When I asked him who it was…
It was Ga-yeon.
So I talked to her.
Were you able to make up your mind
after talking to her?
Yeah.
-And you sat next to me on the first day.
-Yeah.
-We talked quite a bit, didn't we?
Since then, I thought,
"This person is funny."
On the first day, people said that
you chose me because we sat
next to each other for a long time
in the beginning.
THE FIRST DAY, AFTER CHOOSING DATES
I think I know why he chose her.
-The two of you talked the most.
-Yeah.
They stayed next to each other.
I think all of that is true.
I was a bit disappointed by that.
If that was really true,
I wouldn't be his first choice
if someone else sat next to him
in the beginning.
Did you choose me as a safe choice
because I was the first person
you spoke to?
I started having that thought.
I wouldn't have kept talking with you
if I wasn't interested in you.
Don't you think so?
If people were to get paired up
just by sitting next to each other,
everything should've been decided there.
Everyone should have been
paired up with the person next to them.
I think it ended up this way
because it was you.
What do you like about me?
I like your personality
and your appearance
matches my ideal type.
I see.
He said it reassuringly,
so I was satisfied.
Let me ask you. Why was it me?
-You?
-I'm curious.
-Are you curious?
-Yeah.
Now you're curious?
When I first saw you,
you were close to my ideal type.
And when we got to talking,
it seemed like we clicked.
You're calm but subtly funny.
I like that about you.
I like that you aren't over the top.
You said that you don't view
younger guys as men.
I've never viewed younger guys as men.
You remember that?
-Of course.
-Thanks.
It left an impression on me.
It left the strongest impression.
-The strongest impression?
-She doesn't view younger guys as men?
How did you feel after hearing that?
I didn't think much about it.
Why not?
-You were confident?
-I was confident.
Do you still not view me as a man?
-I thought you were confident.
-I am confident.
I just want to know what you think.
I'm at about "Maybe he's not that bad."
I'm keeping the door open.
I see.
I had a very good time.
I feel at ease when I'm with her
and we communicate well.
I think those aspects
are what make us compatible.
I really felt that our feelings
were mutual.
See you later.
CHAE-RIN AND DO-GEON
SECRET DATE ENDS
CAFE MOMENT OF MOMENTS
SECRET DATE
He's here.
-Why did you come so late?
-Did I keep you waiting?
-Yeah.
-What were you doing?
Just waiting.
Really?
The conversations we have
back at the house
and outside are so different.
Not only can I focus on you completely,
I also feel more at ease…
-Really?
-…when I'm with you.
When it's just the two of us…
Do you feel calm?
-I feel calm.
-And?
-I don't feel like I have to try.
-Yeah?
Is how you are around me
close to how you are normally?
It feels like the way I am
when I am truly by myself.
-It feels similar to that?
-Yeah.
Really?
When I look into his eyes,
they look so kind and pure.
But he's smart too.
He's very different from me.
My father made a list of rules for me.
One,
don't show your ignorance.
Two, since I cough a lot,
either do it quietly
or go to the bathroom and do it.
And three,
don't go around farting everywhere.
It fascinates me that
I met someone who is close to
my ideal type.
Don't think too much about it.
Just
accept it for what it is.
There's nothing to dwell on.
I'm serious.
Want to go see the ocean?
Regardless of the secret date,
it's the day before the final decision,
so I wanted to reassure her
of my feelings for her
and that I'll choose her tomorrow.
Ha-yoon calmly expresses
how he feels about me.
He isn't the kind of person
who wants me to open up to him right away.
So when he occasionally reassures me,
I think I am able to open up to him
little by little.
HYE-WON AND HA-YOON
SECRET DATE ENDS
-I'll get going.
-See you.
-Bye.
What?
HEADS THE WRONG WAY FROM THE DOOR
BACKTRACKS
What's going on?
-What's going on?
-What?
-I had no idea.
-About what?
-You requested a secret date with me?
-Yes.
Why?
I wanted to have a chat with you.
-Really?
-Yeah.
We can choose two people, right?
Isn't it up to two people?
-Really?
-Yeah.
I thought we had to choose two people.
I chose her because we are the same age
and I wanted to ask her about things
I was curious about.
When you were the queen,
why did you pair us up like that?
Why did you do that?
I gave hearts to Hye-won.
GAVE HER A LOT OF HEART CHIPS
TO MAKE HYE-WON KING
Ga-yeon and Kyung-ho.
BUT SHE BETRAYED HIM
I felt like everyone had to spray out.
You could spend some time
away from Ga-yeon
and see if you really got jealous.
-To figure that out.
-Really? You thought of all that?
Yeah, I thought of all that.
-And…
-Yeah?
…I thought you and Chae-rin
were a good match.
The queen had a vision in mind.
That's why…
I thought she would feel sorry.
If she felt sorry,
I was going to tell her not to be sorry
and that I rather enjoyed it.
But she wasn't sorry,
so I didn't mention it.
How do you feel?
It's Ga-yeon for me.
I know.
Try to see what's on her mind later.
-What?
-Ga-yeon.
"How do you feel, Ga-yeon?"
"Do you feel the same still?"
Things like that.
-I didn't prepare this--
-You came here to tell me this.
-No. Seriously, I just thought of it.
-Since I'm close with Ga-yeon…
-Since I'm close with Ga-yeon,
-No.
-you came to hear that answer.
He wanted to ask me about Ga-yeon.
It's so funny when I'm with him.
-I had fun, buddy.
-Yeah. Bye.
HYE-WON AND JUNG-MIN
SECRET DATE ENDS
CAFE HAUS HAIL
SECRET DATE
Hey, Ga-yeon.
GA-YEON AND JUNG-MIN
SECRET DATE
It's a secret date, finally.
-Nice to meet you.
You got here early.
About five minutes early?
I'm not sure.
SLURP
We should've gone out yesterday.
I went on a date with Kyung-ho
and had a long chat with him.
So I got an idea about
what kind of person he is
and what he's like in a relationship.
But I have no idea about Jung-min.
I'm going to try my best to figure out
what kind of person he is.
I'm sure I'll have some kind of feeling
during that conversation, right?
I think I'll see what that feeling is
and make my final decision.
-We've only talked back at the house.
-Yeah.
We never got to do it outside.
We never got to have a deep conversation.
I feel more nervous for some reason
-than in front of the fireplace.
-Right?
I feel awkward for some reason.
Yeah.
Until now,
I've dated people
that I have been attracted to.
-Yeah, I'd go for someone…
-That's good.
…I have good feelings about.
That's the kind of relationships I had.
When I was in relationships like that,
I've gotten hurt.
So the man I'd like to date in the future
should be older and settled in life.
Someone who is relaxed
in the way they speak and act?
I want to be in a relationship
where the guy can keep me grounded.
That was my mindset when I came here.
But
when you chose me as the person
you wanted to go on a date with,
we held hands, right?
-We talked while we held hands.
-Yeah.
Would you go on a date with me tomorrow?
I'd love that.
That was huge for me.
I wasn't interested in you at first,
but I opened up to you after that.
That's why I started having
romantic feelings for you.
But my eyes would
drift to where Kyung-ho is sometimes.
I didn't know why though.
I wanted to check my feelings for him.
Then,
I realized that I had romantic feelings
for him too.
But those feelings
were smaller than
the romantic feelings I had for you.
A lot smaller.
Anyway, I've been thinking about it
since last night until this morning.
But I still don't know.
I don't know how I feel exactly.
The person I want to date
and the person I'm attracted to.
The two are so different.
I realized that Ga-yeon was conflicted.
I didn't show it,
but my heart sank.
I was a little unnerved by it.
I thought we got along well
when we hung out.
It was just fun
without thinking about anything.
When we took selfies together,
it was just naturally fun.
My interest in you grew a lot.
That's why I put a lot of Heart Chips
in yours.
I think I'll use up my Heart Chips
and choose you.
But
this is our first date, isn't it?
And we have to decide tomorrow.
I'm a bit sad about that.
You expressed
how you felt about me publicly.
And I responded to that too.
-Acting lovey-dovey?
-Yeah.
I like it and it gets me excited.
-Really?
-Yeah.
Of course.
Even your actions and light touches
have comforted me a lot.
I am thankful but…
"Thanks."
"Heart Chips for Do-geon."
"Thanks. Now, Kyung-ho."
"Thanks!"
No, it wasn't like that.
"Thanks."
"This is hard. Who should I choose?"
Wait. Time out.
-Time out?
-Time out.
I started having feelings for you
when we held hands.
That was very big for me. Tremendously.
What if that wasn't me?
What if that was Kyung-ho?
I don't have to think about it.
It didn't happen.
Really?
Gosh, this won't do.
I have to stay right by your side today.
"Hey, Kyung-ho."
"Shouldn't you sit over there?"
Can I be selfish like that?
I won't give him a chance to get close.
-What do you think about my strategy?
-It'll be funny.
I wanted to hold hands with you
if we went on a date.
Can we hold hands?
Hey.
Are you doing that
because I said this meant a lot?
No, I really was going to
hold your hand as soon as it started.
Give me your hand.
-No.
-Let me help you out.
Give it.
-Let me give you a good tip.
-What?
-It's the last time.
-Just one.
Look.
Hold hands like this.
Hold hands with me…
-And Kyung-ho?
-…and with Kyung-ho too.
-You're insane.
-You'll realize that
you don't feel anything with him.
Maybe you'll think that way.
-You want me to hold hands with Kyung-ho?
-Yeah.
Hold hands with him.
You'll feel it for yourself.
Real nice tip. Real nice.
-I'll get going.
-It ended.
I know.
See you back at the house.
-Shaking hands? Let's lace our fingers.
-No.
-Okay. See you later.
-Okay.
Is this Kyung-ho's seat?
No.
I ought to break this.
-Bye.
-I want to bolt this chair down.
GA-YEON AND JUNG-MIN
SECRET DATE ENDS
I was jealous,
but I didn't think
she would change her mind.
I didn't expect to be so conflicted,
so I did feel bad that Kyung-ho jumped in.
She's the same age as me, right?
She's starting to think about marriage.
-Jung-min would make such a good spouse.
-Totally.
-I think so too.
-Yeah.
That's why she's conflicted.
She's talking about
attraction and whatnot.
-But it's about marriage material.
-Reality.
-Yeah, the reality.
-Right.
GA-YEON IS WAITING FOR ANOTHER
GA-YEON AND KYUNG-HO
SECRET DATE
What did you talk about yesterday?
You and Ye-rim looked
very upset yesterday.
Yesterday? We didn't talk about much.
-Are you curious?
-Yeah.
After our date yesterday,
my mind was somewhat made up,
so I just told Ye-rim that.
I said I like you more.
Why? Is it funny?
It isn't funny.
Why did you laugh?
Anyway…
Both of you looked upset.
-Yeah, we couldn't be in a good mood.
-Right.
So that's how you feel?
I'm only going to express interest in you.
That's that.
Where do you want me to start?
Just tell me what you want to tell me.
-You decide.
-You tell me.
-Okay?
-Do you want me to start from one?
From one to eight.
But eight is most important.
I don't want to know everything.
The latter part is more important.
Then, give me from eight to ten.
No, how about seven to nine?
When we chose our dates,
I told you that Jung-min holding my hand
played a huge part.
SHE ENDED UP STARTED FROM 1
AND ARRIVED NEAR 7
To be honest, our date made me
feel very comfortable.
Yeah.
All the constellations show up like this…
The conversation we had in the car
and the looks we exchanged
kept coming to mind
even after we got back.
Even then, I was still in denial
about my feelings for you.
I wanted to deny it.
-I see.
-Yeah.
But somehow…
That's it.
-So you want to talk?
-I can't make up my mind.
-You can't make up your mind?
-No.
You were in the living room feeling upset.
I was really sleepy that day,
but I didn't want to go in the room
because you were there.
AFTER YE-RIM AND KYUNG-HO
TALKED LAST NIGHT
Why are you doing the dishes now?
I ate out of these.
GA-YEON DREW KYUNG-HO
Didn't I do a good job?
-Didn't I do well?
-You did.
-Good drawing.
-Right?
When you're there, I want to be near you.
Because I felt that way…
This morning,
you were drawing at the table
and Jung-min was lying on the sofa.
But I went over to your side.
Draw an angel too.
I kept feeling like
my body and eyes are drawn to you.
But I don't know what this is.
It's annoying
and I'm confused.
That's how I feel right now.
-You're not sorted out yet?
-No.
If I got a chance to go on a date today,
I wanted to go with Jung-min
because we never got to go on a date.
That's why I wanted to make him king.
I put a lot in yours to make you king.
Why would you make me king?
I wanted you to choose for yourself.
I didn't want that.
But I wanted it.
What if I chose Jung-min
-for the date?
-I thought you would.
Even so?
Yeah.
Then, it would make
Jung-min and me more official.
I wouldn't think that.
I'm only going to think
in a way that benefits me.
It's true that you haven't
gone on a date with Jung-min.
You should've already gone
on a date, but you couldn't.
I still don't know what's right even now.
If I were you,
I'd go with the one I'm drawn to.
If I were you.
I'm not just saying that for my sake.
I really would have done that.
It isn't that I wasn't attracted
to Jung-min at all.
Of course not.
He is kind, considerate,
and he showed subtle physical affection
with or without drawing attention.
I didn't reject all of that.
I let him do it
and it made my heart flutter,
to be honest.
You like physical affection, don't you?
-No.
-Okay.
-Wait.
-What?
What's wrong with light touches?
Yeah.
It was huge for me…
-I'm sure.
-…when we first held hands.
Since I'm confused, Jung-min gave me
a solution before he left.
What did he say?
He said I should hold his hand.
-And…
-I don't want to hear it.
Go ahead.
He said I should hold your hand too.
Then,
he said I'll know.
So I said I won't do it.
You don't want to hold my hand?
-That's not what I mean.
-Okay.
Can you give me your phone for a second?
My phone?
-I'm going to write it down.
-Okay.
I really can't say it out loud.
-Read it when I'm not around.
-Okay.
This is what I want to tell you now,
but it's really what I wanted to tell you
yesterday. Anyway…
Should I rewrite it?
-I'll read it in the car.
-Okay.
Should I delete it?
The way I act when I talk to you
is so different from
the way I act
when I interact with Jung-min.
I'm curious.
It's so different.
If I talk with Jung-min--
Why do you show us different sides?
I become more of an adult.
When I'm talking with Jung-min,
I talk more maturely.
-Really?
-Yeah.
It must be because I'm younger.
Because I'm young.
Yeah.
He flirts in a cute way.
He flirts like a younger guy.
When I'm with Kyung-ho, I can be at ease
while laughing with him.
Then, my heart would skip a beat
out of nowhere.
It must be over.
THE SECRET DATE HAS ENDED
You're going to make your mind up, right?
It's hard. It's so hard.
-You'll do well. You're an adult.
-I'm sure I will.
-Bye.
-Okay.
She may have more feelings for Jung-min.
I don't know if she could tell or not,
but I was nervous.
I didn't feel like
she was leaning toward me.
When I spoke to two different men
in the same place and same spot,
I realized once again that
I act one way with one person
but another way with the other.
When I'm with Jung-min, I become calmer.
It's more fun and my heart flutters too.
But when I am with Kyung-ho,
I feel a bit tense
and I'm left with
lingering feelings afterward.
SHE CHECKS KYUNG-HO'S MESSAGE
AFTER THE DATE
I HOPE YOU CAN ORGANIZE YOUR THOUGHTS
AROUND WHAT'S BEST FOR YOU
He made a signature for me.
I wanted to give her a boost.
I hoped she would
become stronger.
I also hoped she was touched by me.
SECRET DATE
CAFE BONJOUR
Hi.
Hello.
I thought the moment had finally arrived.
"What if I requested him
but he didn't want to talk to me?"
I was worried about that.
Use the blanket.
Did you know I'd ask for you?
You requested me?
Did you request me?
I requested you.
-Really?
-Yeah.
-I requested you too.
-Yeah?
YE-RIM AND KYUNG-HO
SECRET DATE
I regretted what I said when I woke up.
Why?
I think I was argumentative last night.
No, you weren't argumentative.
I was just scolded.
You didn't avoid me today?
-You?
-Yeah.
-No, I tried not to avoid you.
-Really?
But it felt like you were scared of me.
Of course I'm scared of you.
-I'm scared.
-I got scared of you being scared
since you won't speak to me.
I mean…
I tried to stay within your vicinity
and join the conversation.
Yeah, you did.
THIS MORNING
HOVERING AROUND
What's on your mind?
SUDDEN COUNSELING SESSION
I reached out to reconcile last night.
You did.
I admire your courage.
Let's be friends.
Okay.
Thanks.
Do you still feel the same way?
-Feel the same way?
-Yeah.
I…
I choose Ga-yeon.
That's how I feel.
Why?
To be honest,
I don't know if I should
tell you this or not.
-Anyway, I should be honest with you.
-Okay.
I have a younger sister.
She's the same age as you.
Since a long time ago,
when someone is the same age as my sister,
I don't view them as a woman.
I even said that during the pre-meeting.
One sister is five years older than me
and my other sister is
four years younger than me.
But whether it's three, two, one,
five, or six years, it doesn't matter.
Strangely though,
it's weird if they're the same age.
The moment I find out
they're four years younger than me,
it makes me feel distant.
I didn't know
if I should say that to you--
I'm so thankful that you told me that.
You kept saying that age didn't matter.
But I could sense
the immediate distance between us.
22 years old?
We're done for.
What did I do when I was 22?
Are you trying to put distance between us?
But the number two and two
is a bit shocking.
So that was why I felt
the distance between us.
I felt like he was
no longer curious about me.
If you were…
Honestly, if you were a different age,
I really do think things
would have been different.
Get mad at him, Joo-heon.
Anyway, from Kyung-ho's perspective,
the age must have been
a really important issue.
Even if it was important,
he shouldn't have said,
"Things might have been different."
Yeah, he shouldn't have said that.
It would've been better not to say… Hey!
I really do think things
would have been different.
I did think that too.
If I were two years older than you,
you would have liked me
even if I didn't make any effort.
From that aspect,
I'm jealous of Ga-yeon
and I wish I was…
You're right.
It shouldn't be a big deal.
Age is just a number.
-But not 22 years old.
-Right.
Just not that.
What did you want to
-talk about?
-Our conversation?
I don't think I even know
what kind of person you are.
And I wanted you to know
what kind of person I was too.
What kind of person are you?
First of all, I don't like playing games.
Either I like someone or I don't.
Actually,
I did think you would change your mind
if I did my best.
That's why I don't think it's over yet.
Right, it isn't over yet.
Anyway.
Also, I was worried that I was
making you feel uncomfortable.
I didn't want you to feel pressured.
From the moment you said
you were curious about someone else,
I didn't want to make it
uncomfortable for you.
Of course, I want the person I like
to feel at ease.
I really appreciate that.
That's why I waited until
you spoke to me.
You're happy when you meet outside.
Do your feelings grow more than in here?
Only Kyung-ho grilled the meat.
What? I helped out too.
I did that,
but I didn't know
it would turn out like this.
But it isn't over yet.
I know. I'm not that young.
Yeah, I know.
I really tried my best to explain.
Even though he said
he's sure about his feelings for Ga-yeon,
we didn't get to have a real chat.
No regrets?
I'm going to keep knocking like that.
I went into that conversation
with the intention of being
honest and talking about everything
so that I'd have no regrets.
Good job.
-Either way…
-It's better than just pouting.
She found her direction.
As I told you in the beginning,
you really have the face that I am into.
It's embarrassing.
And you actually
have the personality that I like.
I think there's something cool
about people who speak with ease
and kind of nonchalantly.
Do you get close with someone
you met for the first time?
Because I'm not good at that.
When someone appears to be alone
or can't join the conversation,
I appreciated how you picked up on that
and tried to include them.
I've never seen ChatGPT catch bugs.
-If you get the paid version, they do.
-They catch bugs for you?
When you told me your ideal type,
you said the person looks beautiful
when they shine.
There is a moment
when that person really shines,
and that's when they look so beautiful
even if they aren't that pretty.
It's something I would have said.
I was so surprised
when you said those words.
I liked it.
Honestly, I am
so jealous of people who can dance well.
So,
your looks plus your personality,
but on top of that,
you said that was your job.
That's why I totally
fell for you.
She should have said this from the start!
Why say that now?
The moment's already passed.
Do-geon kept telling her that
she should try to change his mind.
She must have gotten
the courage from that.
Do-geon messed everything up but…
-But this--
-Yeah, this one thing.
-He gave her the courage.
-He did.
That's huge.
That's why I totally
fell for you.
That's why
I'm going this far to explain myself.
She made me feel at ease
while we had that conversation.
I thought she was cool.
Even though I didn't intend it,
I did hurt her feelings.
Despite that,
the fact that she was able to say that…
I don't think I could've done that
if I were her.
From where I stand,
you are remarkable.
The way I want someone to be.
Then, let's be friends.
We can be friends. I tried today.
But I don't mean it
the way I said it last night.
The way you said it last night?
What do you mean now?
I want you to open up to me
just a little bit more.
Okay, I won't close the door on you.
I wanted to
try my best for a little longer.
But I'd like you to work with me a little.
Work with you…
I'll work with you.
I'll keep pushing myself to open up too.
It felt like he respected
the weight of my feelings.
As long as it's like this,
I can keep express how I feel to him.
I think it's a relationship
that's worth putting my feelings into.
I was able to express how I felt
as much as I wanted.
That made me feel better.
Ye-rim has matured.
THE SECRET DATE HAS ENDED
See you back at the house.
Anyway, I'll get going.
YE-RIM AND KYUNG-HO'S
SECRET DATE HAS ENDED
ALL THE SECRET DATES HAVE ENDED
KYUNG-HO IS BACK AT THE HOUSE FIRST
Do you know what time it is?
When did you get back?
I got back an hour ago.
-Really?
-No.
About ten minutes ago?
Why are you the only one back?
-I'm the only one here.
-Why?
-I don't know.
-Seriously?
Why would I lie?
-Really?
-Yeah.
Are you not happy about that?
-I'm happy.
-So happy, right?
I love it.
-Seriously?
-Yeah.
We stayed at this house for five days,
so we got used to it.
-I kicked everyone out.
-Good job.
I beat everyone.
-Really?
-Yeah.
But most of the lights were off
and only the dim lights
were on in the hallway.
The atmosphere felt strangely different.
Won't they be back in about ten minutes?
-What a shame.
-One by one.
-Are you sad about that?
-Yeah.
Want something to drink?
Were you able to organize your thoughts?
Yeah, a bit.
I really focused
on myself.
You see,
the way you express how you feel
is so different from how Jung-min does.
Which one do you prefer?
I know, right?
"I know, right?"
-Did you see it?
-Yeah.
It got upgraded. I was wondering
if there was something wrong with my eyes.
-There were colors.
-Yeah.
Then, I saw the heart.
Maybe you have better sense of style
than I do.
-Right?
-Yeah.
You knew how to use the red like this.
It's very…
-interesting.
-What is?
My feelings.
You aren't even going to tell me,
but you say it's interesting and fun.
Because I don't know yet.
-Okay.
-Yeah.
Do you know how to check someone's pulse?
No. How is it?
Isn't it beating fast?
-Isn't it beating really fast?
-It is. Why?
It's right here.
-Here?
-Yeah.
-Do you feel it when you press it?
-I do.
Yours is slow.
-It's slow?
-Yeah.
You're right.
Go.
-Yours is fast.
-Get out.
Yours is the fast one.
I don't know.
It felt strange.
I felt dazed.
She may have captivated me
or I could have been captivated
by that place.
I felt like I didn't have
control over my own mind.
-What about you?
-What?
You must have a lot on your mind.
Yeah, I had a lot on my mind.
But mine has been sorted out.
I don't know what I'm going to do,
but I know how I feel.
I'm just doing
what my heart tells me to do.
Good.
-Good?
-Yeah.
Me too.
This is fun, isn't it?
-Is it fun?
-Yeah.
How can it be fun?
-It isn't fun?
-It's fun.
I don't know anything, but it's fun.
You're the only one that knows.
-But it must be hard because you know.
-Yeah.
What should I do?
What is right?
Neither one is the right answer.
Then, what?
You're just picking
one from the two. Neither one is better.
Jung-min is clear
and straightforward in the way
he expresses himself.
Am I too indirect?
Well, you're similar.
-You are like this.
-Yeah.
Jung-min is like this.
-Really?
-Yeah.
I do go forward.
What if he's already there?
What if he came to me sooner?
Ah. Getting there fast doesn't matter.
You're the one who has to accept him.
-What if he won't give up?
-What?
What if he won't leave my side?
Then, I have to squeeze myself
between you two
if things get bad.
But he hasn't done that, has he?
What if he'll do that from now?
Then,
you come to me.
What if I don't want to do that?
-You don't?
-Yeah.
Can't you?
"I have to briefly go somewhere."
"Oh, right. I have to go change."
Then, come to me.
-Do we have to sit here and wait?
-Right?
I wish I could close the curtains here.
Close the curtains?
-Why?
-Do you want to kiss her?
Imagine there are curtains.
Let's run away to the tent.
-The tent that you hate so much.
-I know.
He should become king,
so the two of them can go to the tent.
YE-RIM IS BACK AT THE HOUSE
Your style is different today.
Today?
The boyfriend look.
Yeah, that was what I was going for.
A clean-cut look.
No, Ye-rim. No.
Go to the room!
Don't go to the living room!
-No, it's better to go to the living room!
-Don't go there!
Go to the room!
-It's better to go to the living room!
-Go to the room!
Did she see? Move away!
-Hey, Ye-rim.
-You're back.
Hi.
Why did you hit me?
Is she okay?
I want to give her a hug.
How did the situation end up like this?
My heart breaks for her. It aches.
-It looks good. Thank you.
-Thank you for the food.
So very, very much.
Why aren't you eating, Ga-yeon?
I'm full.
There's a tear on your shirt.
I'm going for the hot girl look.
-It's the hot girl look.
-Right.
-You look sexy.
-What's that?
Isn't it good?
Have some.
-Just a bit.
-I ate.
-Everyone lost weight.
-You already ate?
I ate a lot.
Did I look like this while playing gonggi?
When is that?
Why do I look so stupid?
Watch carefully.
THE PROBLEMATIC VIDEO
OF DO-GEON PLAYING GONGGI
You should've stopped me
before I did this.
-You should've stopped me.
-I'd make you do it more.
Do-geon playing…
-Do-geon playing gonggi.
Are you okay, sir?
Call an ambulance.
It's okay. It wasn't that bad.
It had a positive effect.
If anything, it makes you more human.
If I got one…
Have a drink at the lounge?
Drink at the lounge?
Why is he so funny?
Drink whenever we meet?
Is this your first meal
since this morning?
Isn't that right?
You didn't eat?
I regretted and was disappointed in myself
that I wasn't more specific.
I could have been more specific
about how it has been
tough for me.
What do you like most? Come on. Stop.
-Are you okay?
-Yeah.
What's up?
I have indigestion.
It's here.
I took medicine twice.
I took it on an empty stomach.
I feel much better now.
-You okay?
-Glad to hear that.
HE HAS A LETTER IN HIS HAND
What could it be?
Du-dum.
-Read it, Jung-min.
-What is it?
-What? What is it now?
"The game will begin.
Go to the lounge now."
-Really?
-Love Marble.
Love Marble?
What is that?
Not Blue Marble, but Love Marble?
Joo-heon!
This game had so much physical contact.
They were holding hands and everything.
-Yeah.
-Remember the coffee-coated peanut?
The worlds are all connected.
It's behind us.
This one.
-Let's watch. This should be fun.
-This is insane.
They're going all out on their last night.
On this final night,
we will now play Love Marble.
-What do you think about me?
-You're pretty.
I was dumbfounded.
Who takes first place in your heart?
Well…
I was confident that she'd choose me.
Is it over for me?
That was when I was
most overwhelmed with excitement.
Should I give him Heart Chip votes?
There are some who are
contemplating leaving some or not.
He held my hand.
My heart raced more
when Jung-min held my hand.
I want to come in.
I wanted the two of us to have a chat.
This is really irritating.
Geez, this is so frustrating.
-To the tent?
-For real?
They already closed the tent.
-You're right.
-That's insane.
I can't control myself.
"It's the day of the final decision."
"Confess how you feel."
Did the subjects,
who always get what they want, win…
I wanted to be true to my feelings
until the end.
…the love they were after?
When you gain something,
you lose something too.
The final decision will begin.
Subtitle translation by: Ilyoung Kim
THE LOVE LAB